A Guide to the Records of the R. H. Lancaster Lodge No. 1370, Grand United Order of Odd Fellows of the State of Virginia, 1890-1910
Alexandria Library, Local History/Special Collections
Alexandria Library, Local History/Special Collections
R. H. Lancaster Lodge No. 1370, Grand United Order of Odd Fellows of the State of Virginia Records 1890-1910
Alexandria Library, Local History/Special Collections
76
This collection consists of correspondence and financial records of the Lancaster Lodge, an Alexandria black fraternal organization. Among the contents are reports, minutes of meetings, dues records and records of elected officers.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Unknown
Scope and Content
This collection consists of correspondence and financial records of the Lancaster Lodge, an Alexandria black fraternal organization. Among the contents are reports, minutes of meetings, dues records and records of elected officers.
Arrangement
Chronological. The financial documents and correspondence are often inseparable. Thus, this collection remains in the order imposed by the donor.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Location of Originals
Entire collection is photocopies.
Contents List
- Financial Records and Correspondence 1890-1911 (Box 76)
  - Financial Records 1890-1893 (Box-folder 76:1)
  - Financial Records 1894-1896 (Box-folder 76:2)
  - Financial Records 1897-1911 (Box-folder 76:3)
  - Correspondence 1890-1892 (Box-folder 76:4)
  - Correspondence 1892 (Box-folder 76:5)
  - Correspondence 1893-1894 (Box-folder 76:6)
  - Correspondence 1895 (Box-folder 76:7)
  - Correspondence 1896 (Box-folder 76:8)
  - Correspondence 1896 (Box-folder 76:9)
  - Correspondence 1897-1898 (Box-folder 76:10)
  - Correspondence 1899-1902 (Box-folder 76:11)
  - Correspondence 1903 (Box-folder 76:12)
  - Correspondence 1904-1905 (Box-folder 76:13)
  - Correspondence 1906-1908 (Box-folder 76:14)
  - Correspondence 1909 (Box-folder 76:15)
  - Correspondence 1910-1911; no date (Box-folder 76:16)
  - Correspondence 1911 (Box-folder 76:17)